Jerome Kern Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Show Music (Box 1-95, Box 103-116)
  - Manuscripts (Box 1-94, Box 103-116)
    - Sally (1920, 1946 revival) lyrics by Clifford Grey and P.G. Wodehouse
      - Greenwich village See also: "Opening act I", Printed piano-vocal scores (2) from Oh, Lady! Lady!!, annotated; 5 p. (Box-folder 47/6)
      - Howard specialty, Ms. full score in ink; 33 p. + p. 8a, 16a, 24a (Box-folder 45/10)
      - Howard specialty, Parts (Box-folder 50/2)
      - It's a hard, hard world [for a man], Photostat of printed piano-vocal score from Oh, Lady! Lady!!; p. 2-5; Negative photostat of above (Box-folder 47/7)
      - Leave it to Jane, Printed piano-vocal score from Leave It to Jane, annotations in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 47/8)
      - [Little] church around [the] corner See also: It's wireless in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Arranger's holograph (Allan Small) full score in pencil; 49 p. (Box-folder 45/11)
      - Church around corner: final chorus See also: It's wireless in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Ms. piano-choral score in pencil; 6 p.; Uniform title: Little church around the corner (Box-folder 47/9)
      - Church around corner: final chorus See also: It's wireless in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Copyist's ms. piano-choral score in ink on transparencies; 5 p.; Ozalids (3) of above, annotated; 5 p.; Uniform title: Little church around the corner (Box-folder 47/9)
      - The church 'round the corner See also: It's wireless in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Printed piano-vocal scores (2), annotations in pencil; 5 p.; Uniform title: Little church around the corner (Box-folder 47/9)
      - Church See also: It's wireless in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music See also: "Opening act II", Ms. sketch in pencil; [1] p.; Uniform title: Little church around the corner (Box-folder 47/9)
      - [Little] church around [the] corner; [Little] church [around the corner] ride-out See also: It's wireless in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Parts (Box-folder 50/3)
      - [Little] church around [the] corner (new); [Little] church [around the corner] ride-out See also: It's wireless in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Parts (Box-folder 50/4)
      - [Little] church [around the corner] ride-out See also: It's wireless in Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music, Arranger's holograph (Allan Small) full score in pencil; 6 p. (Box-folder 45/12)
      - Look for the silver lining, Ms. full score in ink; 21 p. (Box-folder 45/13)
      - Look for the silver lining: #3, Parts (Box-folder 50/5)
      - Look for the silver lining [utility], Ms. full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 45/14)
      - [Look for the] silver lining utility, Parts (Box-folder 50/6)
      - Looking all over [for you], Ms. full score in ink; 87 p. (Box-folder 108/1)
      - Looking all over [for you] exit, Ms. full score in ink; 4 p.; Note: originally from The Cabaret Girl (Box-folder 108/1)
      - I'm looking all over, Ms. sketch in pencil; [1] p.; Uniform title: Looking all over for you (Box-folder 47/10)
      - Looking all over -- last 4 bars and tag, Ms. choral arrangement in pencil; [1] p.; Uniform title: Looking all over for you (Box-folder 47/10)
      - Looking all over for you, Photostats (2) of printed piano-vocal score; p. 104-105 only; Negative photostat of printed piano-vocal score; p. 104-107 (Box-folder 47/10)
      - Looking all over [for you], Parts (Box-folder 51/1)
      - Napoleon: #4, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink and pencil; 5 p.; Note: originally used in Have a Heart (Box-folder 47/11)
      - On the beam see: Reaching for the stars
      - On with the dance, Printed piano-vocal scores (3); 5 p. (Box-folder 47/12)
      - Opening [act I] See also: "Greenwich village", Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 34 p. (Box-folder 46/1)
      - Opening, Ms. sketch in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 47/13)
      - Opening: #1, Parts (Box-folder 51/2)
      - Opening act II See also: "Little church around the corner", Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 34 p. (Box-folder 46/2)
      - New opening act II, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 7 p.; Note: some water damage; Uniform title: Opening act 2 (Box-folder 46/3)
      - New opening act II, Parts; Uniform title: Opening act 2 (Box-folder 51/3)
      - Opening act II, Ms. sketch in pencil; [7] p. (Box-folder 47/14)
      - Opening act II, Ms. piano score in pencil; 4 p. (Box-folder 47/14)
      - Opening act II, Ms. lead sheet (conductor's) in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 47/14)
      - Opening act II, Parts (Box-folder 51/4)
      - Overture, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-33, 50-53 (odd numberings) (Box-folder 46/4)
      - Overture, Parts (Box-folder 51/5)
      - Reaching for the stars, Ms. full score in pencil and ink; p. 1, 16-79, 84, 89-90; Note: same music as "On the beam" from You Were Never Lovelier (Box-folder 46/5)
      - Reaching for the stars, Ms. piano-choral score in pencil; [8] p. (Box-folder 48/1)
      - Reaching for the stars, Copyist's ms. piano-choral score in ink on transparencies; 8 p.; Ozalids (3) of above (Box-folder 48/1)
      - Reaching for the stars, Ms. lead sheet in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 48/1)
      - Reaching for the stars, Ms. sketch in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 48/1)
      - On the beam: 2nd dance chorus, Ms. sketch in ink and pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 48/1)
      - On the beam, Printed piano-vocal scores (3) from You Were Never Lovelier (film), pasteovers and annotations; 5 p. (Box-folder 48/1)
      - Reaching for the stars, Parts (Box-folder 51/6)
      - Sally, Printed piano-vocal score with altered lyric for burthen in Kern's hand (pencil); 5 p. (Box-folder 48/2)
      - Sally and I, Ms. full score in ink; 21 p. (Box-folder 46/6)
      - Sally and I, Parts (Box-folder 51/7)
      - Sally and I: reprise 1, Parts (Box-folder 52/1)
      - Sally and I: 2nd reprise, Parts (Box-folder 52/2)
      - Sally and I: melodrame, Ms. piano score in pencil; [1] p. (incomplete) (Box-folder 48/3)
      - Sally's dance, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 17 p. (Box-folder 46/7)
      - Sally's dance, Ms. sketch in pencil and ink; [3] p. (Box-folder 48/4)
      - Sally's dance, Ms. piano score (conductor's) in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 48/4)
      - Sally's dance, Ms. piano score in pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 48/4)
      - Sally's dance: #6, Parts (Box-folder 52/3)
      - Same sort of girl, Printed piano-vocal score from The Girl From Utah; 5 p. (Box-folder 48/5)
      - Schnitza-Komisski, Ms. full score in ink; 19 p. (Box-folder 46/8)
      - The Schnitza-Komisski, Ms. lead sheet in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 48/6)
      - The Schnitza-Komisski, Copyist's ms. lead sheet in ink, 2 copies; 3 p. (Box-folder 48/6)
      - Schnitza-Komisski, Parts (Box-folder 52/4)
      - Schnitza-Komisski: encore, Parts (Box-folder 52/5)
      - Siren's song, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 32 p.; Note: originally from Leave It to Jane (Box-folder 46/9)
      - Chorus of the siren's song, Ms. choral score in pencil; [2] p.; Uniform title: Siren's song (Box-folder 48/7)
      - The siren's song: chorus, Copyist's ms. choral score in ink on transparencies; 2 p.; Ozalids (3) of above, annotated; Uniform title: Siren's song (Box-folder 48/7)
      - Siren song: after vocal and surf dance, Ms. lead sheet (conductor's) in pencil; [2] p.; Uniform title: Siren's song (Box-folder 48/7)
      - Siren song: after vocal -- and into surf dance at sight cue, Ms. lead sheet in pencil; [2] p.; Uniform title: Siren's song (Box-folder 48/7)
      - The siren's song: female back ground, Ms. choral score in pencil; 3 p.; Uniform title: Siren's song (Box-folder 48/7)
      - The siren's song: female back ground, Copyist's ms. choral score in ink on transparencies; 3 p.; Ozalids (3) of above, annotated; Uniform title: Siren's song (Box-folder 48/7)
      - The siren's song, Printed piano-vocal scores (4) from Leave It to Jane, pasteovers and annotations; 5 p. (Box-folder 48/7)
      - Siren's song: #8, Parts (Box-folder 52/6)
      - Tulip time [in Sing Sing], Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 14 p.; Note: originally "Dear old fashioned prison of mine" from Sitting Pretty (Box-folder 46/10)
      - Tulip time in Sing Sing, Printed piano-vocal scores (2) from Sitting Pretty, pasteovers and annotations; 5 p. (Box-folder 48/8)
      - Tulip time: male 4, Ms. choral score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 48/8)
      - Tulip time [in Sing Sing]: #5, Parts (Box-folder 52/7)
      - Whip-poor-will waltz, Ms. full score in pencil; 18 p. + p. 21⁄2 + 2nd p. 18 (Box-folder 46/11)
      - Whip-poor-will specialty, Ms. full score in pencil; 22 p. (Box-folder 46/11)
      - Whip-poor-will, Printed piano-vocal score, annotated; 7 p. (Box-folder 48/9)
      - Whip-poor-will specialty, Ms. short score in pencil, incomplete; [5] p. (Box-folder 48/9)
      - Specialty before waltz (whip-poor-will), Ms. sketch in pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 48/9)
      - Specialty after whip-poor-will, Ms. lead sheet in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 48/9)
      - Specialty after whip-poor-will dance, Ms. piano score sketch in pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 48/9)
      - Whip-poor-will waltz, Parts (Box-folder 52/8)
      - [Whip-poor-will] waltz incidental, Parts (Box-folder 52/9)
      - Wild rose, Arranger's holograph (Bennett & unidentified) full score in ink and pencil; 59 p. (Box-folder 47/1)
      - Wild rose (3rd section), Ms. full score in ink; 29 p. (Box-folder 47/1)
      - Wild rose, Ms. sketch in ink and pencil; [3] p.; Includes: section of "Sally's dance" (Box-folder 48/10)
      - Wild rose, Ms. lead sheet (conductor's) in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 48/10)
      - Wild rose, Ms. lead sheet (p. 1-8) and short score (p. 9-12) in pencil; 12 p. (Box-folder 48/10)
      - Wild rose: male chorus, Ms. melody line in pencil; [8] measures (Box-folder 48/10)
      - Wild rose: male chorus and Sally, Ms. choral score in pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 48/10)
      - Wild rose: male chorus and Sally, Copyist's ms. choral score in ink on transparencies; 3 p.; Ozalids (4) of above, annotated; Note: appended to 1 copy is a 4 p. ms. lead sheet extension (Box-folder 48/10)
      - Wild rose, Printed piano-vocal scores (2), annotated; 5 p. (Box-folder 48/10)
      - Wild rose, Printed piano-vocal score from film version of Sally, annotated; 5 p. (Box-folder 48/10)
      - Wild rose: #10, Parts (Box-folder 53/1)
      - Wild rose utility, Parts (Box-folder 53/2)
      - You found me and I found you, Printed piano-vocal scores (2) from Oh Lady! Lady!!; 5 p.; Note: inscription on 1 copy ascribes missing p. 3-4 to "'Looking all over) conductor's Book" (Box-folder 48/11)
      - You're here and I'm here, Ms. lead sheet in pencil + 16 measure piano score revision; [2] p. + pasteover (Box-folder 48/12)
      - You're here and I'm here, Printed piano-vocal score (probably from The Marrage Market), annotated; p. 3-5 (Box-folder 48/12)
      - Sally, Printed piano-vocal score from the London production of 1920-21; 132 p.; Includes: "The butterfly ballet" by Victor Herbert (Box-folder 48/13)
      - [Miscellaneous sketch fragments], Ms. sketches in ink and pencil; Includes: "Reaching for the stars" "Wild rose" "Sally's dance" "Whip-poor-will [Specialty]" (Box-folder 48/14)
      - [Miscellaneous parts], Ms. parts (Box-folder 53/3)
      - [Lyric sheets], Typed lyric sheets, some annotated; [30] p.; Includes: All alone All you need is a girl Blood Bungalow in Quogue Greenwich village Look for the silver lining Looking all over for you Napoleon Reaching for [the] stars Schnitza-Komisky Schnitzka Komisski Wild rose (Box-folder 48/15)
      - [Miscellaneous items]: Ms. song listings and notes (Box-folder 48/16)
    - She's a Good Fellow (1919) lyrics by Anne Caldwell
      - Froggies' patrol, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink and pencil; 20 p.; Uniform title: Bullfrog patrol (Box-folder 54/1)
      - I'll make it up: patrol, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 20 p.; Uniform title: Bullfrog patrol (Box-folder 54/2)
      - The bullfrog patrol: The blues patrol, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink; 12 p. (Box-folder 54/3)
      - [The bumble bee], Holograph piano score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 54/4)
      - Entrance of girls see: Miscellaneous/Unidentified Show Music
      - Ginger town, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink and red pencil; 11 p. (Box-folder 54/5)
      - Ginger town: Make believe, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in pencil; 4 p. (Box-folder 54/6)
      - Home sweet home, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 20 p. (Box-folder 54/7)
      - Duet: Jacquiline and Hoppy, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink; 10 p.; Note: probably the same music as for "Over the hills"; Uniform title: Home sweet home (Box-folder 54/8)
      - I beleive in signs see: Opening act III
      - Encore -- in the Navy, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 7 p.; Uniform title: In the Navy (Box-folder 54/9)
      - Letter song, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 12 p.; Uniform title: Just a little line (Box-folder 54/10)
      - A little pep, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 25 p. (Box-folder 54/11)
      - A little pep, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, part of lyric in Kern's hand; 7 p.; On back: ms. sketch in pencil of the Duncan sisters' "Smiles" (Box-folder 54/12)
      - Opening act III: [I believe in signs], Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 32 p. (Box-folder 54/13)
      - Sketch for opening act III, Holograph lead sheet with piano score intro, in ink; 3 p.; Uniform title: Opening act 3 (Box-folder 54/14)
      - Opening act III, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 7 p.; Note: also known as "I believe in signs"; Uniform title: Opening act 3 (Box-folder 54/14)
      - Scene music: act III, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 17 p. (Box-folder 54/15)
      - Scene music, Holograph sketch in pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 54/16)
      - Semiramis, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 35 p. (Box-folder 54/17)
      - Semiramis: duet, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink; 4 p. (Box-folder 54/18)
      - Wine, women and song, Arranger's holograph (Frank Saddler) full score in ink; 10 p. (Box-folder 54/19)
      - Wine, women and song: duet: Chester & Pollard: act I, Ms. lead sheet in ink; [1] p.; On back: ms. sketch in pencil of the Duncan sisters' "Mammy's blues" (Box-folder 54/20)
      - Wine, women and song: duet: Chester & Pollard: act I, Ms. lead sheet in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/20)
      - Wine, women and song, Ms. (Frank Saddler) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; [4] p. (Box-folder 54/20)
      - Refrain -- wine, women & song, Parts; Uniform title: Wine, women and song (Box-folder 54/21)
    - Show Boat (1927) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Aborigines number See also: "Dahomey", Ms. piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; 7 p. (Box-folder 58/1)
      - Aborigines number See also: "Dahomey", Copyist's ms. choral score in ink, no lyric; [2] p. (Box-folder 58/1)
      - *After the ball, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 20 p.; Music by Charles K. Harris (Box-folder 55/1)
      - *After the ball: #32, Parts; Note: "Hot time: #32a" included in some of the parts (Box-folder 60/1)
      - Andy and Parthy: #28, Parts (Box-folder 60/2)
      - Andy trocadero: #31a, Parts (Box-folder 60/3)
      - Apache [dance], Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 12 p.; Note: features "Valse des Rayons" from Offenbach's ballet Le Papillon (Box-folder 55/2)
      - Bill, Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 14 p. (Box-folder 55/3)
      - Bill, Ms. (Leonid Raab) piano-vocal score in ink; [3] p. (Box-folder 58/2)
      - Bill, Proof for printed piano-vocal score, annotations in pencil; p. 3-5 (Box-folder 58/2)
      - Bill: #25: [in Bb], Parts; Includes instructional performance note in pencil from George Hirst; [1] p. (Box-folder 60/4)
      - Bill: [in Ab], Parts (Box-folder 60/5)
      - Boarding house - finale: #23, Parts (incomplete) (Box-folder 60/6)
      - Box office scene, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 47 p.; Includes: "I would like to play a lover's part" (Box-folder 55/4)
      - Cake walk, Ms. piano score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 58/3)
      - Can't help lovin' dat man, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 28 p. (Box-folder 55/5)
      - Can't help loving dat man, Ms. (possibly Victor Young's) full score in ink; 19 p.; Note: this is the arrangement for Helen Morgan's recording on Brunswick (Box-folder 55/6)
      - Can't help lovin' dat man, Holograph sketch in ink; [3] p.; Note: dummy lyric by Kern (Box-folder 58/4)
      - Can't help lovin' dat man, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink and pencil, for publication; 6 p. (Box-folder 58/4)
      - Can't help lovin' that man, Violin part only (Box-folder 60/7)
      - Captain Andy: #12, Parts (Box-folder 60/8)
      - Change of scene: #9a, Parts (Box-folder 60/9)
      - Chaser, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; [5] p.; Note: music based on "Why do I love you?" (Box-folder 55/7)
      - Chaser: #34, Parts (Box-folder 60/10)
      - Chaser: #38, Parts (Box-folder 60/11)
      - Cheer up: new verse, etc., Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 6 p.; Note: became "I might fall back on you" (Box-folder 55/8)
      - Cheer up!: act II scene I, Holograph sketch in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 58/5)
      - Cheer up: #13, #15a, Parts (Box-folder 61/1)
      - C'mon folks see: Queenie's outburst
      - Colored blood, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-2, 4, 1-11, 17-32, 12-23, 45-46, 24-29, 54, 30-32, 33-38 [60 p. total]; Note: became "Mis'ry's comin' aroun'" (Box-folder 55/9)
      - [Colored blood scene], Holograph and ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score/sketch in ink, no lyric; 10 p.; Note on p. 6: "Sketches for Wasserman scene" (Box-folder 58/6)
      - Colored blood scene, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 2 p. (incomplete) (Box-folder 58/6)
      - The convent, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 23 p. (Box-folder 55/10)
      - The convent: act II scene IV, Holograph piano-vocal score in ink; 6 p. (Box-folder 58/7)
      - The convent: #27, Parts (Box-folder 61/2)
      - Cotton Blossom: last scene, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 3 p. (Box-folder 55/11)
      - Dahomey See also: "Aborigines number", Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 26 p. (Box-folder 55/12)
      - [Dahomey]: 4 measures vamp, Holograph piano score (3 p.) in ink and rhythmic sketch (1 p.) in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 58/8)
      - Dahomey: #21, #19: [1st version], Parts (Box-folder 61/3)
      - Dahomey: #21, #19: [2nd version], Parts (Box-folder 61/4)
      - Dance number, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 30 p.; Note: additional music on the back of 3 p. includes an alternate ending; Note: written for either the London or Paris production; Uniform title: Dance away the night (Box-folder 55/13)
      - Duettino (Magnolia & Ravenal): act I scene V, Holograph piano-vocal score/sketch in ink, no lyric; [2] p.; Note: from "Box office scene"; replaced by "Ballyhoo" (Box-folder 58/9)
      - Encore to #5: #'s 11a, 15, Parts (Box-folder 61/5)
      - Entr'acte: #18, Parts (Box-folder 61/6)
      - Finale act I, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-40, 40b, 41-59, 61-64; Note: crossed out p. 60 ("Why do I love you?") is on back of 2nd p. 31 (Box-folder 56/1)
      - Final act I, Photocopy of holograph piano-vocal score/sketch in ink, no lyric; 7 p. (Box-folder 58/10)
      - Finale act I: #17, #14, Parts (Box-folder 62/1)
      - Finale acte II, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; [2] p.; Note: for Paris production (Box-folder 56/2)
      - Finale ultimo: #37: [in C], Parts (Box-folder 62/2)
      - Finale ultimo: #37: [in D], Parts (Box-folder 62/3)
      - Sketch. Frank & Elly, Holograph sketch in ink, lyric for refrain by Hammerstein in pencil, dummy lyric for verse by Kern; [1] p.; Note: probably "My girl"; Uniform title: Frank & Elly (Box-folder 58/11)
      - Gallivantin' aroun' see: Series II -- Miscellaneous Music
      - *[Goodbye my] lady love: #31, Parts; Music by Joe Howard (Box-folder 62/4)
      - Harmonica number: act I scene V, Photocopy of holograph piano-vocal score in ink, no lyric; 2 p. (Box-folder 58/12)
      - Hey, fella!, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 16 p. (Box-folder 56/3)
      - [Hey, fella!]: E major, Holograph sketch in ink, lyric for verse only in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 58/13)
      - Hey, fella!, Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 58/13)
      - Hey, fella!: #34, Parts (Box-folder 62/5)
      - *[A] hot time [in the old town tonight]: #32a See also: "After the ball" parts, Parts (incomplete); Music by Theodore M. Metz (Box-folder 62/6)
      - *[A] hot time [in the old town] tonight, Parts (Box-folder 62/7)
      - I might fall back on you see: Cheer up see: Terzetto
      - I would like to play a lover's part see: Box office scene
      - Imitations and buck dance, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-8, 91⁄2, 9-24 (Box-folder 56/4)
      - Imitation: #36, Parts (Box-folder 63/1)
      - Imitations: #36, Parts (Box-folder 63/2)
      - It's getting hotter in the North see: No Mason Dixon Line
      - Letter scene: #22, Parts (Box-folder 63/3)
      - Life on the stage See also: Ruby Keeler's dance from Lucky, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 22 p.; Uniform title: Life upon the wicked stage (Box-folder 56/5)
      - Life on the stage; #'s 8, 12a See also: Ruby Keeler's dance from Lucky, Parts; Uniform title: Life upon the wicked stage (Box-folder 63/4)
      - A lover's part: opening box office scene: act I scene V, Holograph sketch in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 58/14)
      - [A lover's part], Ms. (Robert Russell Bennett) piano-vocal score in ink; p. 9-14; Note: cues in Kern's hand in pencil (Box-folder 58/14)
      - Magnolia and Julie See also: "Scena (Magnolia and Julie)", Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink; 28 p.; Note: first strain derived from the railway duet "If we were on our honeymoon" from Doll Girl (Box-folder 56/6)
      - Magnolia & Julie: #5a, Parts (Box-folder 63/5)
      - Make believe see: Opening chorus
      - Segue "Make believe": act I scene I, Holograph piano-vocal score/sketch in ink, some dummy lyrics by Kern; 2 p.; Uniform title: Make believe (Box-folder 58/15)
      - Make-believe, Ms. (Leonid Raab) piano-vocal score in ink, annotations in pencil; 5 p. (Box-folder 58/15)
      - Make-believe, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in pencil; 8 p. (incomplete) (Box-folder 58/15)
      - Make believe: incid.: #'s 7, 26a, Parts (Box-folder 63/6)
      - Melos: act I scene I: Ravenal & Magnolia, Holograph sketch in ink and pencil; [2] p.; Note: heavily crossed out (Box-folder 58/16)
      - Mis'ry's comin' aroun' see: Colored blood
      - My girl see: Frank & Elly